<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Text page for the Arena galaxy content (clusters.xml/sectors.xml/gamestarts.xml),
  English (language 44). PLAUSIBLE, not VERIFIED: page/path naming convention
  (t/0001-L044.xml, page id 20206) follows the standard X4 text-file pattern, not
  confirmed against this extension in-game.
-->
<language id="44">
  <page id="20206">
    <t id="9001">XMultiplayer Arena</t>
    <t id="9002">A dedicated, empty arena cluster for XMultiplayer PvP sessions.</t>
    <t id="9003">Arena Sector</t>
    <t id="9004">An empty sector reserved for XMultiplayer arena duels.</t>
    <t id="9005">XMultiplayer Arena</t>
    <t id="9006">Start a dedicated PvP arena session. No factions, no economy, no jobs -- just you, your opponent, and empty space.</t>
    <t id="9007">You have joined an XMultiplayer arena session. Wait for your opponent to connect, then fight.</t>
    <t id="9008">Arena Pilot</t>
    <t id="9009">Arena Fighter</t>
    <!-- A5 map variants (PlanMod.md 1.1). -->
    <t id="9010">XMultiplayer Arena: Asteroid Field</t>
    <t id="9011">A dedicated arena cluster for XMultiplayer PvP sessions, set in a dense asteroid field.</t>
    <t id="9012">XMultiplayer Arena: Debris Field</t>
    <t id="9013">A dedicated arena cluster for XMultiplayer PvP sessions, set in a drifting debris field.</t>
    <t id="9014">XMultiplayer Arena: Nebula</t>
    <t id="9015">A dedicated arena cluster for XMultiplayer PvP sessions, set in a dense nebula.</t>
    <t id="9016">Arena Sector (Asteroid Field)</t>
    <t id="9017">An asteroid-field sector reserved for XMultiplayer arena duels.</t>
    <t id="9018">Arena Sector (Debris Field)</t>
    <t id="9019">A debris-field sector reserved for XMultiplayer arena duels.</t>
    <t id="9020">Arena Sector (Nebula)</t>
    <t id="9021">A nebula sector reserved for XMultiplayer arena duels.</t>
    <t id="9022">XMultiplayer Arena: Asteroid Field</t>
    <t id="9023">Start a dedicated PvP arena session amid a dense asteroid field. No factions, no economy, no jobs -- just you, your opponent, and the rocks.</t>
    <t id="9024">XMultiplayer Arena: Debris Field</t>
    <t id="9025">Start a dedicated PvP arena session amid a drifting debris field. No factions, no economy, no jobs -- just you, your opponent, and the wreckage.</t>
    <t id="9026">XMultiplayer Arena: Nebula</t>
    <t id="9027">Start a dedicated PvP arena session inside a dense nebula. No factions, no economy, no jobs -- just you, your opponent, and reduced visibility.</t>
  </page>
</language>
